Photo Good morning Durgesh ji
Good morning madam online interview so
exactly how are you that
you that Amit accused and first of all I am
Ambaram Durgesh Shukla and I
live in Baroda I have
completed my graduation from Government Patel University
Anand and I am an inspector office I like to
play cricket and listen to music there are
total four members in my Chinese family there is
father mother and a younger brother my father is a
layer in a factory my mother is a housewife
and my younger brother is working he is a
spray in seventh standard thank you
absolutely if we talk about my relationship then
I am very positive about my career and life I am
honest and
motivated and working and if I
talk about my business then sometimes such occasions
come when someone asks me for help I am
not able to refuse him and because of that I
also get trapped myself ok so this was it exactly
as you know I
am a pressure so right now I have character
knowledge but whatever roles and
responsibilities will be given to me by the company
I  I will request you to complete it with hundred percent accuracy. A very
good Durgesh and as
I saw, your Ribbon Meghna has
told you about this foundation very well. The
foundation trains warriors like us and
after completing the training, they
help in getting jobs. So I want to get
training in this case from there and fellow admin
please is helping in getting jobs.
So can you tell me your annual vacation.
A as I told you that I am starting my career, so
salary is not my first
practice. I want to
start my career with your organization
so that I can always add to my skills and knowledge.
My thing ends here.
A thank you so much ma'am. You started
asking me questions to reach out to me, so I would
like to know that you will remember the next process
if you please it will be
good and also tell you the further problems
on the call.
I am Kimam thank you so much for your
opinion. I am in trouble, please do it.
[Music]
Ajay